#### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

Name: Vinod Kumar Kathi

Address: Værebrovej 14,2,3, 2880 Bagsværd

Mobile no: +45 31 49 34 56

E-mail: vinod2rahul@gmail.com

Date of birth: 15th March 1982

Civil status: Married Nationality: Indian

Visa status: Permanent residence in Denmark

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To work at the position of an administrator/Support and utilize my technical skills to manage the computerized systems employed at the organization. To gain effective experience in installing systems and correcting errors to ensure trouble-free technical support for the employees.

#### **SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES**

- Knowledge of Mac, Linux, and Windows
- Enthusiastic to learn new technologies and ability to work in groups to complete the desired task
- Supported and maintained LAN/WAN and related equipment
- Diagnosed and resolved all network-related issues
- Performed troubleshooting of end-user security
- Configured end-user devices such as laptops/desktops, printers, and shared office equipment
- Assisted office personnel with Chain Box, network and computer problems, provided troubleshooting and owned issues to resolution.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **IT Support**

Skovbrynet Skole Gladsaxe Kommune

Nov.2019 to March 2020

#### Responsibilities:

- Setup new computers Windows and MAC to teacher by installing Airwatch and all necessary programs
- Setting new loan computers/Ipads to bibliotek
- Deleted data in old computers/Ipads
- Solved Uni/aula login issue to teacher by adding @gladskole.nu
- Solved IP shared printer issues
- Made **julekalender 2019** with all staff picture and message on info screen
- Invloed router and access point setup for skole exams
- Solving classroom Projector and Apple Tv issues.

## **IT Support**

Bon Appetit Group A/S May 2016 – feb 2018

## Responsibilities:

- Supported and maintained LAN/WAN and related equipment
- Configured end-user devices such as laptops/desktops, printers, and shared office equipment
- Diagnosed and resolved all Chain Box and network related issues
- Assisted office personnel with network and computer problems, provided troubleshooting and owned issues to resolution
- Designed Templates, newsletters and advertisements for Information Screen.

## **GIS Associate**

Tech Mahindra Limited, India Nov.2007 – June.2010

## Responsibilities:

- Work on extensions of existing Client based tool called BISON using C++
- Design, build and maintain an efficient and reliable C++ code
- Suggest and implement improvements in current products
- Basic Database systems indexes, filters.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages C, C++, HTML, CSS, PHP
Operating systems Windows /7/10, MAC OS
Databases Oracle, MySQL, SQL.

Tools Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Premiere Pro

# **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION**

- Master's degree in computer science from Osmania University Hyderabad-India 2007
- Bachelor's degree in computer science from Kakatiya University Warangal-India 2004.

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

Voluntary work: Working as a Graphic Designer for Telugu community in Denmark.

www.denmarkteluguassociation.com

Game: Cricket.

# **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that the above information is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Copenhagen. (Vinod Kumar)